apropos-conservatories.com 2011-04-27

# Apropos - Privacy Policy

####  Data protection act

This is the apropos tectonic privacy statement which applies to the entire website. Any future changes will be posted on this website. We have structured our website so that, in general, you can visit it without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. If however, you choose to provide us with any information by which you can be identified, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. We are registered under the Data Protection Act 1998.

####  Data collection

We may collect the following information:

  * Personal information is required, when submitting an enquiry to us. This includes name, address, telephone numbers, email address.

  * Additional contact information may also be required in order to provide you with additional site functionality and further correspondence about our products and services.

  * Cookies are used within some of the site for interactive devices.

####  How do we use the information we gather?

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.

  * To improve our products and services.

  * Our representatives may contact you, either by e-mail, phone or mail, as part of our customer care procedures.

  * We may periodically send promotional information about new products, special offers or other information, which we think you may find interesting using the contact details, you provided by requesting information from us.

  * We may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes occasionally, be it by e-mail, phone or mail.

####  Are your personal details shared with third parties?

If you have not advised us otherwise, when using this site you are agreeing that we may use your personal information for other purposes. This may include sending personal information to a third party company. However, we have taken measurable steps to ensure the same level of data protection is practised by such companies.

If you have not previously objected to us using your personal information for either of these purposes you may change your mind at any time by writing to us at:

apropos tectonic  
Greenside House  
Richmond Street  
Ashton Under Lyne  
OL6 7ES

####  website links

Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites, and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

####  what are cookies and will they harm my computer?

A cookie is a piece of text, which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive (via your browser). Once agreed, your browser adds that text in a small file. A cookie helps analyse web traffic or helps the use of our online chat facility and interactive devices. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. This practice is strictly adhered to. We know that people have concerns about cookies, but we believe that the benefit we both gain from their proper use is worthwhile. You may set your web browser (Microsoft Internet Explorer or Netscape Navigator) to notify you of cookie placement requests or decline cookies completely. You can delete the files that contain cookies - those files are stored as part of your Internet browser.
